

Pramote Supnoi

Full stack developer

- /pramotesupnoi
- in /in/pramote-supnoi +6695-169-9021

About me

Hello, I'm Pramote Supnoi. You can call me James. I'm a freelance software developer with 5 years experience living in Thailand. I can develop variety kind of software such as web app, AR/VR app, game, cross platform mobile app, rest api. I believe in efficiency and clean code. If you have any questions, feel free to contact me anytime! my contact information is inside this page.

Education

2012 - 2016

Bachelor of science Information Technology (Software development) GPA 3.45

at Udon Thani Rajabhat University

Experiences

May 2015 - July 2015

Internship student @AT Creative Solution Co.,Ltd.

May 2017 - Oct 2019

Full stack developer @Softcare Co.,Ltd.

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

AR/VR developer

@VVR Asia Co.,Ltd.

Oct 2020 - Present

Full stack, AR/VR developer @Freelancer

Professional skills

JavaScript React, JQuery

THTML

CSS

PHP

Drawing

Windows form app

FastAPI

Python

C# .Net

Additional skills

Photoshop

DBMS

Game, AR/VR

🙀 Unity3D

MS Office

SQL server, MySql, Firebase,

MongoDB

Certifications and awards

- Microsoft Offce Certification 2014 at Khon Kaen University
- Bronze medal certification in Mathematical ability creative contest using The Geometer's Sketchpad 2010 at Satrirachinuthit School
- at Santapon college Second place in Microsoft Word competition 2010

Second place in Microsoft Power Point competition 2009

at Udon Thani Rajabhat University

Participated in a National Software Contest (NSC) 17th Final Round 2015

Activities

- at Fasion Island Shopping Mall, Bangkok Participated in a National Software Contest (NSC) 18th Final Round 2016
 - at Mahisorn Hall, Siam Commercial Bank PCL., Head Office. Bangkok Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2015
 - Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2016 at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

- Lecturer about How to create mobile game with Unity3D 2016 at Nakhon Ratchasima Rajabhat Univerisity
- Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2021 at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2020

Thailand's Mental Health Center #8 : Mental health assessment system

The online assessment for teacher and parent use to evaluate their student/child mental health problem and if they have sign of a problem the system will suggest the way to handle the problem. Also this system allow student/child to evaluate

Accomplishments

- themself and will open for general user in the future. Using PHP, MySql, ReactJS, Bootstrap and some others library in development process. My role in this project is designing website appearance, coding (front end & back end), designing system and database. Gift Angel Radio radio station website Website for #1 radio station in Udon Thani, Thailand. Using PHP, MySql, JavaScript, Bootstrap and some others library in development process. This website can manage news, DJ, radio schedule, top chart list, sponsor, page appearance. My
- role in this project is designing website appearance, coding (front end & back) end), create rest api for mobile application, designing system and database. Hintang village's E-Commerce website E-commerce website that sell handmade product by elderly from Hintang village, Udon Thani, Thailand. Using PHP, MySql, JavaScript and some others library in development process. My role in this project is create website layout following the design, coding (front end & back end), designing system and database.
- Udon Thani Rajabhat University Teacher evaluation system Teacher Evaluation System for Udon Thani Rajabhat University. Using PHP, MySql, JavaScript and some others library in development process. This system allow admin to create a work evaluation schedule and let the teachers in the university to send their works to calculate the amount of salary raise they will get in the university's budget year. My role in this project is create page layout following the design, coding (front end & back end), designing system and database.
- Flyflow Studio Gym & Fitness membership system Membership system for Flyflow Studio Gym in Fitness center. Using .NET C#, SQL Server in development process. This system use to manage members, fitness course, promotion, register course for members, collect and process data when members come to use gym's services, print receipt and reports, calculate daily, monthly, yearly income. The system is a windows application. My role in this

project is designing layout, coding, designing system and database.

Mr.Khwanchai Suksaen

Teacher

+6689-715-6151

khwanchai.s@gmail.com

Reference

^{*} Some projects can not be mention due to client confidentiality